那个早晨与往常无异 非常宁静
It was an uneventful morning -- quiet.
把每一集《单身汉》都保存下来
instead of saving every episode of "The bachelor,"
你干嘛不直接拿
Why don't you just hit yourself
大锤子砸你的头
on the head with a sledgehammer?!
爸爸 音乐声调小点
Dad, turn down that song!
*办不到*
* No can do *
孩子们周五放假
The kids had a Friday off of school,
所以我们接上曼尼
so we picked up Manny
去我们最爱的薄饼店
and went to our favorite pancake place --
放松一下嘛
Relaxing.
米奇尔 你好
Mitchell, hi.
什么
What?!
让他跟小卡说
Oh, have him tell Cam
我一小时后去接他打壁球
I'll pick him up for racquetball in an hour.
这么吵我根本听不见他说什么
I can't even hear him it's so loud.
-大家都闭嘴好吗 -真讨厌
- Can everybody just shut up?! - I hate it.
很抱歉 总之
Sorry about that. Anyway...
你好
Hello.
你好 请问是菲尔·邓垃圾桶吗
Hello. Is this Phil Dumpster?
干嘛 格尔
What do you want, Gil?
没搞错吧 等等
Got to be kidding me. Hang on.
我需要你代表我们两人
I need you to send a gift to mom
送一份生日礼物给妈妈
for her birthday from the both of us.
不行 去年就是我送的
No, I did it last year.
我知道 但我要你再送一次
I know, and I need you to do it again.
听我说 1点20分我有个电话会议
Look, I've got a conference call at 1:20.
之后卢克的家教要来家里
Then Luke's tutor comes to the house,
45分有个销售会议
45 sales meeting,
我还得送艾丽克斯去上柔道课
and I still got to get Alex to judo.
但你还是挤出时间来找我无理取闹了
And yet you somehow found time to bitch at me.
你还真是事业生活两不误啊
You really can have it all.
说真的 随便给她买张礼品卡就行了
Honestly, just get her a stupid gift card,
你个大号婴儿
you big baby!
为什么事情一碰到他就都这么麻烦
Why does everything with him have be so dramatic?
我们为什么要停下来
Why are we stopping?
太好了
Hey. Oh. Perfect.
你先是在电话里斥责我
Okay, first you berate me on the phone,
现在又亲自来我办公室斥责我
Then you show up to my office and berate me in per--
这是什么情况 我不喜欢这样
Oh, w-what is this? I don't care for this.
我们出车祸了
We got in an accident.
天呐
Oh, my God!
我们差点出车祸了
We almost got in an accident.
这差很多好吗
That seems like a really important distinction.
一辆大卡车
There was this big truck,
闯过停车标志
and it barreled through a stop sign,
差几英寸我们就撞上了
And it missed our car by inches.
天呐 大家都没事吧
Oh, my God! And everyone's okay?
没事 只是都吓坏了
Yes, just very shaken up.
但是 米奇尔 我真的很抱歉
But, Mitchell, I am so sorry
刚才朝你大喊大叫
that I yelled at you before.
我把送给老妈的生日贺卡带来了
Look, I brought you the birthday card for mom,
-你也签个名 -好 谢谢
- And you can sign it. - Okay. Thank you.
给我们最好的朋友
"To our best friend."
有点讽刺啊 这是她的生日啊
That's a little sarcastic. It's her birthday.
不 我是真心的
No, I mean it.
米奇尔 我差点就死了
Mitchell, I almost died.
我希望给我们的老妈过个很棒的生日
I want our mom to have a great birthday.
又来了
Oh, and we're doing this again.
-好吧 天呐 -是啊
- Okay. Oh, god. - Yeah.
你好 我一会儿就过去
Hi. I'll be there in a sec, yeah.
我的取证会被提前了
Okay, my deposition got moved up.
太好了
That's great.
我得把所有事情都改期
So I'll just have to move everything -- you know what?
-我得在车上吃饭 然后 -不不不
- I'm gonna eat in the car and then- - No, no, no, no, no.
不不不 给我 给我
No, no, no. Give it, give it!
你知道我差点死掉之前在做什么吗
Do you know what I was doing right before I almost died?
跟你现在做的一样
Exactly what you're doing.
纵容自己的亲人瞎胡闹吗
Humoring a relative?
不是 我在安排我人生中的每一分钟
No, no, scheduling my life down to the last minute.
你看看这个
I mean, look at this --
下午4点17分打电话给纽约办公室
"Call New York office -- 4:17 p.m."
你有没有发现除了我们两个
Do you realize that everybody
大家都以5分钟为计算时间的最小单位
but us rounds up to the nearest five minutes?
米奇尔 今天的事情让我意识到
Today made me realize something, Mitchell.
我不想当那种
No, I don't want to
按分钟规划时间的人 你呢
be a 4:17 kind of person. Do you?
我想
Yes, I do.
因为那通电话必须在4点23分前打完
'cause that phone call needs to be done by 4:23
否则到4点41分我就死定了
so that I am not a dead man by 4:41.
把手机还我
Give me my phone.
不不不 快给我 克莱尔
Nope. Nope. No. Give me -- Claire.
我们要一起去做点什么
We're gonna do something together.
来吧 今天请假吧
Yes, take the rest of the day off.
办不到
I can't do that.
你可以的 我就请假了
Yes, you can. I did!
是啊 因为你是给你老爸打工
Yeah, 'cause you work for your father.
不不不 我们必须这么做 米奇尔
No, no, no, we need this, Mitchell.
真的必须这样
We really need this.
克莱尔 我今天真的很忙
Claire, I'm really swamped today, and I --
拜托拜托拜托拜托
Pleeeeeeeeeeeeeeeease...
好了 快走吧
Stop. Just go.
拜托拜托我们能滑慢点吗
Pleeeeease can we slow down?
你快把我的手腕磨破了
You're chafing my wrist.
别再装你不喜欢这样了
Don't pretend you're not loving this.
好吧 我刚刚滑过一泡尿
Okay. All right. I think I just skated through some pee.
现在我们能回去了吗
C-can we go back now?
不行
No!
不 因为我们不是预约狂魔
No, because we are not appointment-making control freaks.
我们在找乐子呢
We are having fun.
你是在找乐子 我是被你逼的
You are. I'm just doing what you're making me do.
好吧 停下
Okay, okay, stop.
不不不不不
No, no, no. No, no, no.
我们回去吧 回去吧 回去吧
Let's go back, let's go back, let's go back.
为什么 为什么非要现在回去
Why? Why do we have to go back now?
为什么 我明白了 明白了
Why -- oh, I get it. I get it.
你还在怕从地下通道里滑过去是吧
You're still scared to skate through the underpass.
什么叫"还在"
What do you mean, "Still"?
什么叫"害怕" 什么地下通道
What do you mean, "scared"? What underpass?
米奇尔 你11岁时
Mitchell, you were 11 years old,
妈妈让我带你一起
and mom made me take you with me
和我朋友索菲·金去玩轮滑
when I was skating with my friend Sophie King,
地下通道很黑 所以你害怕
and you were terrified to go through the underpass
不敢过去
'cause it was dark,
你还说里面肯定都是怪物
and you were sure it was filled with monsters,
所以我们把你甩掉了
so we ditched you.
我根本都不记得了
I don't remember this at all.
我边滑走边叫你"大号婴儿"
Yeah, I skated away and called you a big baby.
索菲朝我扔了块石头
Sophie threw a rock at me
你还吼我"你真像个基佬"
and you yelled, "You're so gay."
我是喊了
I did do that.
是不是
Oh, didn't I?
我们原来老用那个词儿
We used to use that word a lot.
说谁都能用"基佬"
You used to be able to call anything gay.
你怀念吗
Do you ever miss that?
不
No.
那很伤人
That's hurtful.
是啊
Yeah.
对不起 米奇尔
I'm sorry, Mitchell.
你当时那么害怕
You were scared,
我应该拉紧你的手走过通道的
and I should've held your hand through the tunnel,
我不是...一个好姐姐
and I was -- I was not a good big sister.
对不起 你能原谅我吗
I'm so sorry. Will you forgive me?
-原谅 -原谅了吗
- Yes, yes. - You do?
-原谅 我原谅你了 -我爱你
- Yes! I forgive you. - I love you.
-我也爱你 -爱你哦
- Love you, too. - Love you!
好了
Okay, okay. Okay.
-我们滑起来 -对 我们滑
- Let's do this. - Yes, let's do this.
-过来 -什么 干什么
- Come on. - What? What's happening?
不是 我们要滑过通道
No, no, no, we're going -- we're going through the tunnel.
不 老天爷啊 不要
No. God, no. No, no, no.
不行 你得克服自己
Oh, no, you got to get over this.
-不 好吧 -好啦 你放松
- No! All right. - Okay. Just let yourself go.
-就随它吧 -好 我可以的
- Just let it go. Just -- you know? - Yep. I'm good.
对 你得穿过去
Uh, yeah, you got to get past it.
不 不 不 不要 克莱尔
N-n-no. No, no! No! N-n-no! Claire, no!
不要啊
N-n-no! N-no!
被分开那瞬间我挺抱歉的
I felt bad when we got separated,
但我知道
but I knew that when he skated out
等他在通道另一端出来的时候
the other side of that tunnel,
一个心理伤疤会痊愈的
an emotional scar would've been healed.
米奇尔 米奇尔
Mitchell?! Mitchell?
不 不要啊 不要
No! N-no! N-n-no! N-no!
天啊 怎么了 怎么了
Oh, my god! What happened? What happened?
-太恐怖了 -然后呢
- It w-- it was terrible! -Yes.
他们把我的钱包 轮滑鞋和领带都抢了
They took my wallet and my skates and my tie.
一个流浪汉要领带干嘛使
What -- what homeless person needs a tie?
天啊 太对不起了 米奇尔
Oh, my god. I am so sorry, Mitchell!
好了 能把我手机还给我吗
Okay, um... Can you give me my phone?
我得注销银行卡
'cause I got to, you know, cancel my cards.
好 给 给你 希望还有电
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, god. I hope you have juice.
这一天震死我了
That thing has been buzzing like crazy.
天呐 好吧
Oh, god! Okay. Okay.
我的会议被提前了
My meeting's been pushed up.
15分钟后就要开始了
It's in 15 minutes.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay. Okay, okay.
看着我 看着我
Look at me. Look at me.
这是个测试 我们不为小事忧心
This is a test, and we don't sweat the small stuff.
-就随它吧 -够了 停
- Just let it go. - Stop it! Stop it.
我知道你觉得找到了新自我
I know you think you discovered the new you,
但你在努力不去控制别人的时候
but you are controlling
仍然是个彻头彻尾的控制狂
even when you're trying to not be controlling.
所以 把轮滑鞋给我
So j-- give me your skates.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
我被你拖了这么远
You've dragged me so far,
现在我离办公室比离我们的车要近
we're closer to my office than we are to the car.
脱鞋
Take 'em off!
他还是没准备好
He just wasn't ready.
但我呢
But me?
我要让那些曾经掌控我生活的
I had a message for the small stuff
小事情知道我的讯息
that used to rule my life.
菲尔 亲爱的 你怎么样
Hey, Phil. Honey, how you holding up?
很好
Good.
我在沙滩这 长话短说
So, I'm at the beach -- long story.
你介不介意在家等着
Anyway, I was hoping you wouldn't mind
卢克的家教来
waiting at the house for Luke's tutor.
我介意 很介意
Actually, I would mind. I'd mind quite a bit.
我这很忙
I'm kind of busy.
好的 很好
Okay, great.
去死吧 鸡毛蒜皮的小事
Suck it, small stuff.
我们为什么停下
Why are we stopping?
对许多人来说 濒死体验是一种警钟
For many, a near-miss with death is a wake-up call.
但当你差一点就没赶上差一点就死的体验
But when a man misses his own near-miss,
才会真正醒悟自己错失了什么
he truly sees what he's been missing.
我的梦想经不起等待
No more putting my dreams on hold.
五年前 我做了一个遗愿清单
Five years ago, I made a bucket list.
是时候开始行动了
It was time to start crossing things off.
人生恐怖瞬间之极
Scariest moment of my life.
天啊 我还以为失去你了
Oh, my gosh. I thought I lost you!
但神奇的是 有好事发生了
But amazingly, something great came out of it.
我知道姐姐对我的真感情了
I found out how my sister truly feels about me.
姑娘们 真的吗
Girls, are you sure?
真的 我们走回家
Positive. We'll walk home.
我们差点就死了
We almost died.
是啊
Yeah.
你在车里说的那句...
A-about what you said in the car...
拜托现在不要取笑我
Please don't make fun of me right now.
没 我永远不会取笑你的
No, I would never.
其实你说得好坦诚
It was actually really honest.
我不该再挖苦你的智商了
And I need to stop taking shots at your intelligence.
你也不是经常那样做
You don't do it that often.
因为很多次你都没听出来
Well, you miss a lot of it.
看哪 我又那样做了
There, I did it again.
做什么了
Did what?
无关紧要
Uh, it doesn't matter.
我一直认为你是很自私的人
I always considered you to be this self-absorbed person,
不过其实你挺有深度的 是吧
but you're more substantial than that, aren't you?
谢谢你
Thank you.
这样吧 我今天不去学柔道了
You know what? I'm blowing off judo today.
我们一起玩
Let's hang out.
我们做什么好呢
What should we do?
给你改变造型
Makeovers.
好吧
Okay.
太好了
Great!
我们会路过我做蜜蜡脱毛的地方
We're gonna walk right past my waxing place.
跟你的女士小胡须说再见吧
Say goodbye to that gal stache.
如果舒服的话 那所有人都是辣妹了
If it were easy, everyone would be hot.
是 但不仅是高跟鞋让我的脚疼
Yep, you know, I-it's not just my feet.
是我不慎撞到了停车标志牌上面
It's from when I walked into the stop sign
因为你不肯还给我...
because you wouldn't give me back my --
好吧 把你的眼镜还给你 拿着
Okay, fine. I'll give you back your man-goggles. Here.
我只是以为回家的路上
I just thought we might run into
我们可能会遇到几个帅哥
some cute boys on the way home,
不过 幸好没有遇到
but it's probably best we didn't.
你的嘴唇又红又肿
That's a pretty angry lip you got there.
真的吗
Really?
别人都会这么红吗
Does everybody's get this red?
你的汗毛太多了
Well, you had quite a bit of growth.
我本来还想让那个女人处理一下你的胳膊
I was gonna have that lady take a crack at your arms,
不过她的围裙都被汗湿透了
but she had already sweat through her apron.
天呐
Oh, my gosh!
我新指甲的照片已经得到一百个赞了
I already have 100 likes on my picture of my new nails.
告诉你一声 照片背景里好像有我
Um, FYI, I'm -- I'm sort of in the background there,
脱毛时尖叫的样子
screaming mid-wax.
四百个人对此照片点赞
400 people liked this photo.
我不是其中之一
I was not one of them.
我的美术老师
My art teacher
留了个关于"蓝调时期"的短评
made a pithy "Blue period" comment,
而我的头号候选舞会舞伴
and my top prom prospect
突然找了个加拿大女朋友
suddenly found a girlfriend in Canada.
你能不能把运动鞋还给我
Do you think I could get my sneakers back?
你去试衣服的时候
Ohh, I threw them away with the rest of your clothes
我把你的鞋和衣服都扔了
when you were in the changing room.
我本来想把它们送给管家的
I thought about saving them for the housekeeper,
可我不记得她是不是有儿子
but I couldn't remember if she had a son.
听着 我已经很努力地在忍受你...
Look, I've tried really hard to put up with a lot since...
怎么了
What's going on?
跟你在一起真开心
Oh, I just had so much fun with you!
我们一起玩的机会太少了
We don't do this enough.
真希望有什么可以让你教我的
I just wish there was something that you could teach me.
等等 你教我柔道怎么样
Wait, what about your judo stuff?
你不会感兴趣的
Uh you're not interested in that.
才不是 我有兴趣 来嘛
No! No! I am! Come on!
来个斜劈还是什么的
Karate-chop me or something!
那不是...
That is not --
好吧 我教你
Okay. All right.
我们先做一个简单的动作
Let's just do one simple move.
好的
Okay.
不会弄皱我的上衣吧
Now, this won't wrinkle my top, will it?
这可太有意思了
That was actually fun!
再教我一次
Show me one more time.
不
Oh, no!
天呐 我以为又失去你了呢
Oh, my gosh. I thought I lost you again.
等等 倒回去 又是怎么回事
Wait, wait, wait. Back up. Again?
是啊 差点出车祸的时候
Oh, yeah, when we almost got killed,
我以为把手机摔坏了
I thought I lost my phone.
那可真恐怖
It was really scary.
曼妥思喷射器 第二次测试
Mentos-pramp-climb, test number two.
经验教训 当压力达到危险等级
Lesson learned -- when pressure builds to dangerous levels,
必须得到释放
it must be released.
是你的嘴好些了 还是你的脸变红了
Is your lip getting better or your face getting redder?
我去客厅啦
Just gonna pop into the family room.
你在搞什么
What the hell was that?!
这才刚刚开始呢
Oh, I'm just getting started!
为什么你要这样傻...
Why do you have to be such a silly --
海莉 住手
Haley, stop!
妈妈
Mom!
菲尔 亲爱的
Phil, honey.
我本来就心情沉重
I was already on edge.
前一天 我和妈妈在公园
The day before, I was with my mom at the park
有个骑自行车的人抢走了她的手机
when some guy on a bike swiped her phone.
他一定是个惯犯
He must have been a criminal mastermind.
只那一秒她没在给乔拍照
He struck the one second she wasn't
就被他抓住了
taking pictures of Joe.
最糟的是 我眼看着他抢走手机
The worst part is, I saw him grab it.
我本来有机会做点什么
I had a chance to do something
在妈妈面前做个英雄的 可我僵住了
and be a hero to my mom, but I froze.
你会怎么做
What would you have done,
使他成为讽刺漫画的主角吗
made him the subject of a satirical cartoon?
那些漫画曾扳倒过总统
Hey! Uh, they've taken down presidents.
你能不能支持我一下
Now, can you just support me here?
并没有多少机会可以让儿子为...
There are only so many moments a son has a chance to --
真成熟
Very mature.
挑起事端 然后又不理我了吗
Pick a fight then tune me out?
我才不在乎 停下
It's not bothering me. Stop it!
爸爸 音乐声调小点
Dad, turn down that song!
*办不到*
*No can do.*
你确定吗 曼尼
You sure, Manny?
是的 我走回家
Positive. I-I'll walk home.
-我们差点死了 -是啊
- We almost died. - Yeah.
白人
White.
是的 我确定
Yes, I'm sure.
有那么难想象犯罪的是白人吗
Why is it so hard for you to imagine
就算大多数罪犯都是...
that a criminal can be white when most of the --
你说单车的颜色啊
Ah, the bicycle.
是的 是白色
Yes, yes, it was white.
你手机不是被偷了吗
I thought your phone got stolen?
这是乔的手机
This is Joe's phone.
所以恐怖分子才痛恨我们
This is why the terrorists hate us.
整个世界冰冷无情
The universe is cold and unfeeling.
唯一不变的只有混乱
The only constant is chaos.
巧克力薄饼又卖光了吗
Was that place out of chocolate-chip pancakes again?
我们差点被卡车撞死
We were all almost killed by a truck.
我的天啊 你没事吧 宝贝
Ay Dios mio! Are you okay, papi?
都是菲尔的错对吧
This was all Phil's fault, wasn't it?
他老是听那种该死的新潮音乐
He's always blaring that damn new wave music!
不 他急转弯避开了
No. He swerved to avoid it.
救了我的命
Saved my life.
不过生命无法自主
But the game of life is rigged.
死亡不可避免
Death always win.
好了 我知道你现在需要什么
Okay, I know what you need right now --
去冰淇淋店
A trip to the ice-cream shop.
他不需要冰淇淋
He doesn't need ice cream.
他要讲讲刚才发生的事
He needs to talk about what just happened to him.
我可以去吃点冰淇淋的
Well, I could go for some ice cream.
我知道怎么安慰我儿子
I know how to fix my son.
就这么安慰吗
So, this is fixed.
绕过去
Go around.
平时为了尊重你
Normally, I'd be avoiding these cracks
我都尽量避免这样的时刻
out of respect of your back, Mom,
可过了今天好像都没有意义了
But after today, it seems pointless.
够了 上车
That's it. Get in.
不要 杰 他害怕
No, Jay, he's afraid!
这样只会更糟
It's only gonna get worse.
上车 相信我
In. Trust me.
上车五分钟他就会春光灿烂了
Five minutes in here, he'll be happy as a clam.
妈妈呀
Aah! Mama!
冷静
Calm down.
这主意很烂
This was a bad idea.
下车
Hop out.
这就对了 杰 要等他准备好
Good for you, Jay. It has to be when he is ready.
-不 他来开 -什么
- Nope. He's driving. - What?
什么 我做不到
What? I-I can't.
你给我开
You're doing it now.
神啊 开车吧
Jesus, take the wheel.
他坐后面就够害怕的了
He's terrified to be in the back.
现在你要让他坐前座
Now you're gonna put him in the front seat
这样他就能把我们都弄死了
so that he can kill all of us?!
你能别火上浇油了吗
Can you not make this fear worse?
我看过米奇尔怕黑的时候
I watched Dede coddle Mitchell
迪迪是怎么过分呵护他的
when he was afraid of the dark.
他到七岁还是眨眼每次只眨一边
Till he was seven, he'd only blink one eye at a time --
害得不少女生误会了
gave a lot of girls a very wrong idea.
曼尼 你不想这么做对吧
Manny, you don't want to do this right?
不 我不想
No, I really don't.
好的 宝贝 要不我们换吧
Okay, papi, you know what? Let's switch.
我来开
I'm going to drive.
妈妈 我很怕[我有个美人儿]
I've got a bombshell, mom.
宝贝 多谢 但是我们这个姿势
Ay, papi, thank you, but this is a very weird thing
说这种话太诡异了
to say when we're in this position.
不 我决定永远不开车了
No, I've decided I'm never driving.
不行
No way.
你坐这 你坐那
You there. You there.
按我说的做
We're doing this my way.
每次都是要么按你说的做
Ah, yeah, 'cause it's your way
要么就滚蛋[上高速]
or the highway.
天啊 不要上高速
Oh, God. Not the highway.
你一直让我像个父亲一样教导他
You always want me to be his dad.
我这不是在做吗
Well, I'm being his dad.
我真的好怕 杰
Oh, uh, I-I'm really scared, Jay.
这就是我们要解决的问题
This is what we're fixing.
我还是个孩子的时候
Look, when I was a kid,
住在一个巨大的吓人的黑色湖旁
I lived by a big, scary black lake.
我一直觉得湖里有怪兽
I always thought there monsters in there and whatnot.
一天晚上 我爸把我拉下床
One night, my dad dragged me out of bed
然后直接把我踹进湖里
and tossed me right in that cold water.
然后我就再也不怕那个湖了
I was never scared of that lake again.
踩油门吧
Now, give it some gas.
妈妈啊
Mma! Aah!
这个喊妈妈的习惯也要改一下
That's another habit I wouldn't mind breaking,
不过我们现在必须要
but, you know, right now we...have to...
我在干什么呢
Oh, what am I doing?
我讨厌我爸那样对我
I hated my dad for that.
最后我怕的不是湖 变成他了
I ended up scared of him, not the lake.
曼尼 没事
Manny, - it's okay.
那边 骑车那个
Over there! On the bike!
是偷我手机的那个白人
The white guy that stole my phone!
我没看到有人
I don't see anyone.
就是他 他刚拐弯
Yes! He just turned the corner!
偷手机贼 他要逃走了
The phone burglar! He's getting away!
这一次不会了
Not this time.
前面左转
Up there to the left!
我什么人都没看到
I don't see anyone!
我也没看到 我乱说的
I didn't see anyone either. I made it up.
我可不要
I am not going to
到了儿子40岁时还得开车载他
drive my son around until he's 40.
唯一能战胜曼尼的恐惧的
The only thing stronger than Manny's fear
是他保护他的妈妈的愿望
is his need to protect his mama.
不 他跑了
Oh, no! He got away!
但是你做得很不错
But you did very good, Manny.
我刚刚开得超快
That was a frickin' rush!
但我不会放弃 我们会抓到那个人的
But we're not giving up. We're gonna find that guy.
不
No!
你确定要这样吗
Are you sure about this?
你们走吧 我走路回家
Just go. I'm walking home.
我听不见他说话 太吵了
I can't even hear him, it's so loud.
你们能闭嘴吗
Can everybody just shut up?!
-你好 -请问是菲尔·邓垃圾桶吗
- Hello. - Hello. Is this Phil Dumpster?
干嘛 格尔
What do you want, Gil?
没搞错吧 等等
Got to be kidding me. Hang on.
是你的极品娇妻在说话吗
Is that your hot wife I hear?
她还在上那些瑜伽课吗
Hey, is she still taking those yoga classes?
我要挂了
Hanging up.
等等 就说一句话
W-w-wait. Wait. Real quick.
锡达街225号的房子归我管了
The listing at 225 Cedar Street,it's mine now.
你居然偷了我的房子
You poached my listing?
不仅偷了 还给它调了味
Poached it, seasoned it,
顺便加了索普蛋白酱呢 哥们
and covered it in Thorpe-andaise sauce, my friend.
你该谢谢我 傻邓
You should thank me, dumpy.
你又退居二线了
You're back in second place
不过你还能看到美景
with your favorite view...
那就是我的后背
my sweet behind.
为什么事情一碰到他就都这么麻烦
Why does everything with him have to be so dramatic?
我们为什么要停下来
Why are we stopping?
天呐 我以为我失去你了
Oh, my God! I thought I lost you.
能说什么呢
What's to tell?
卡车开过了停车标示 我避开了卡车
A truck runs a stop sign, I avoid it,
大家都走开了 有惊无险
everyone walks away, bing, bang, no boom.
-那可是辆卡车 -太吓人了
- There was a truck! - That was crazy!
大家都冷静一下 别激动
Everybody calm down. Calm down. Let's not overreact.
-你说什么 -老爸
- What?! - Dad!
-我们差点就死了 -是啊
- We were almost just killed! - Yes!
没错 差点 也就是说我们都没事
Exactly. Almost, which means we're all just fine.
你就没有一点点后怕吗
You aren't the least bit upset?
今天早上我吃的华夫饼上有奶油笑脸
It's gonna take more than that to ruin a morning
要毁掉这样美好的早晨可没这么容易
that started with a whipped-cream smile on my waffle.
其实我是受了点影响
Okay, it may have affected me a little,
但有时要明白自己的感受并不容易
but sometimes it's hard to know what you're feeling.
我当时在想之后的壁球训练
Mostly, I was thinking about racquetball later
我要给小卡狠狠来一招
and hopefully giving Cam a nice spanking.
说明一下 今早的壁球训练
Fair warning, may be working out some anger issues
我可能要发泄一下情绪
on the racquetball court this morning.
-别问原因 -没问题
- Don't ask. - Sounds good.
我们新买的烘干机到了
So, we're getting our new dryer delivered.
应该是蛋壳白色的
It's supposed to be eggshell,
但送来的不是蛋壳白 是纯白色
but, oh, it's not eggshell, it's white.
我当时正在跟送货员吵架
Anyway, I'm laying into the delivery driver,
结果米奇尔插进来说"没关系"
and Mitchell strolls in and says, "Oh, it's fine,"
还给送货员一块香蕉面包
and then offers him a piece of his banana loaf.
真是气人
I heard that.
哪怕一次也好 我希望
Just once, I would like
米奇尔站在我这边
Mitchell to take my side.
每次我都会替他说话
I am constantly strolling in and saving him
就像拯救困在塔中的公主
like a little princess in the tower.
有时候我也想当公主
Sometimes I'd like to be the princess.
-怎样都是一样 对吧 -什么
- Six of one, right? - What?
我们为什么在这里停
Why are, why are we stopping?
我不明白 菲利普
I'm-I'm very confused, Phillip.
相信我 这房子会以索普光速卖出的
Trust me, this house is gonna sell at Thorpe speed.
你们好
Hey, guys.
-菲尔 -看来你知道了 抱歉
- Oh, hey, Phil. - I guess you heard. I'm sorry.
没关系 这事时有发生
Oh, no, it happens all the time.
我就是过来给你们一点良心建议
I just stopped by to give you guys a little care package
以证明我完全没有介怀
to show you there's no hard feelings.
非常有绅士风度 邓菲虫
Class act, Dung beetle.
这是专攻不法行为案件的律师的名片
Here's the Malpractice Attorney
大部分他的客户受到伤害后都找这个律师
most of his clients have used after he's ripped them off.
你们可能会失眠
You will be losing some sleep,
这种药总能帮我妻子入睡
but these have always helped my wife.
这个神父已经退休了
And this priest is retired,
但他应该还在主持驱魔活动
but I think he still does exorcisms,
今天过后你们会需要的
which you'll need after today.
-菲尔 -没关系的
- Listen, Phil—- - It’s okay.
看见一个曾经中庸的地产经纪堕落如此
It's sad, really, to see a once-mediocre realtor
也挺让人伤心的
reduced to this.
格尔 别这样 好好说话
Gil, please, let's keep this civil.
还有 如果你再对我老婆出言不敬
Oh, by the way, if you ever speak disrespectfully again
我会杀了你
about my wife, I'll kill you.
抱歉 我说得好像这是个玩笑
Sorry. That sounded like a joke.
我真的会杀了你
I will actually kill you.
总之 如果你们能清醒过来
Anyhow, when you guys wake up
闻到硫磺的味道
and smell the sulfur,
这是其它地产经纪的名单
here's a list of other realtors,
如果想找我 我九点上班
and if you need me, I'll be in the office at 9:00,
还是十点吧 我要去看牙医
10:00. I have the dentist.
这是怎么回事
Where did that come from?
人生苦短 不能被恐惧操控
Life's too short to be ruled by fear.
公主 我们去
What do you say
把你想要的那台烘干机要来怎样
we get you the right dryer, princess?
天呐
Oh, my.
菲尔平常很...
I mean, Phil is usually just so...
但那天他很...
but then he was just, like, so...
接着还变得更...
and then he got even more...
我无能为力
There's nothing I can do.
-我不接受 -办不到
- I can't go for that. - No can do.
卡梅隆买了一台蛋壳白的烘干机
Cameron here bought an eggshell dryer.
不是纯白 不是燕麦色
Not white, not oatmeal,
不是瑞士咖啡白
not Swiss-coffee,
不是爽身粉白 也不是骨白
not baby-powder, not bone.
是蛋壳白 你叫罗伯是吧[抢劫]
Eggshell. Look, Rob, is it?
这名字真有趣
That's interesting.
接下来是这样
Here's how this is going down--
没有蛋壳白的烘干机我们不会走
we don't leave without that eggshell dryer.
不是天鹅羽毛白 不是切斯特猪白
Not swan-feather, not chester-pig-white.
颜色已经说得够清楚了
I think we've covered the colors.
我每天都卖房子给不同的人
I sell houses to people every day
他们会问我去哪买烘干机比较好
who ask me where they should buy their dryer.
你不希望我告诉他们哪家不能去吧
I don't think you want me giving them any static.
后面可能还有一台
I may have one in the back.
但要两个人把它从车上搬下来
But it takes two guys to load the truck,
今天这里只有我一人
and it's just me today.
是吗
Is it?
就在那电光火石的一瞬
It was right about then
我的心头涌上一个问题
that a question started nagging at me.
菲尔性感吗
Is Phil sexy?
你想跟我做点疯狂的事吗
You feel like doing something a little crazy with me?
什么 不想 什么 不想
What? No. What? No.
你好啊 亲爱的
Hey, honey.
菲尔 亲爱的 你还好吗
Phil, honey, how you holding up?
挺好的
Good.
我在沙滩 说来话长
I'm at the beach -- long story.
我希望你不介意
I was hoping you wouldn't mind
在家等着卢克的补习老师
waiting at the house for Luke's tutor.
实际上 我挺介意的 我做不到啊
Actually, I would mind. I'd mind quite a bit.
-我挺忙的 -好吧
- I'm kind of busy. - Okay.
小卡 有件事是克莱尔永远不会允许的
Cam, there's something that Claire would never approve of
但却是我一直都想做的
that I've always wanted to do.
一直吗
Always?
我们要在后车座上铺块毛毯
We're gonna want to put a blanket down on that backseat.
这是个巨大的错误
This was a huge mistake.
我跟一只多毛的秘鲁神兽被困在后车座
I am jammed in the backseat with a hairy Peruvian biter.
简直是92年的春假情景重演
It's spring break '92 all over again!
前方有减速带 把绳子拉紧一点
Well, speed bump coming up. Hold the leash taut.
那样可以让它保持镇静
It's supposed to keep her calm.
我挺走运的 这家伙不喜欢吐口水
I got lucky. I don't think this one's a spitter.
我话说太早了
uh, I spoke too soon.
你这样觉得吗 真是够了 快停车
You think? That's it. Pull over.
菲尔 我也想支持你的
You know, Phil, I wanted to support you on this.
我坚决支持在家里养牲畜
I'm a firm believer in livestock in the home,
但你实在是太失控了
But you are out of control.
不 一切完全在我掌控之中
No, I'm in control -- more than ever.
如果我为了让自己称心如意
And if me getting what I want
而给别人稍微带来了一点点麻烦
inconveniences people a little,
随便吧
then so be it.
它紧张了
Uh, she's nervous.
饲养员说你该让它舔你的头发
The guy said you should let her suck on your hair.
好了 够了 我不干了
Okay, that is it. I am done.
一切的荒唐到此为止
Enough of this ridiculousness.
谢你了啊 菲尔
And thank you, Phil,
因为你让我意识到了米奇尔的好
For making me appreciate Mitchell.
他或许是有一些缺点
He may have his faults,
但至少他不是个疯子
but at least he's not a crazy person.
菲尔 亲爱的
Phil, honey.
在呢 克莱尔
Yes, Claire.
我又搞了匹草泥马回家
I got an alpaca -- again.
你不能发表任何不满的意见
And there's nothing you can say about it.
我不会发表任何意见的 有什么问题啊
I'm not saying anything. What's the problem?
妈 爸
Mom, dad!
客厅里有头骆驼
There is a camel in the living room!
那不是骆...
It's not a c--
-我做不到 -好了
- I-I just can't. - Okay.
看来你们都见过乔琳2号了吧
I see you've all met Jolene two.
不幸的是 你妈强迫我
Sadly, the original Jolene
退回去的那头乔琳
that your mother made me return
被一家儿童医院残忍地收养了
was cruelly adopted by a children's hospital.
今早那辆卡车没有把我撞死
You see, something hit me this morning
但却把我的脑子撞开了窍
when that truck didn't hit me this morning --
我一直都没有真正掌控自己的人生
I have not been in control of my own life.
但那种日子到此为止了
But those days are done.
看来我真是无法掌控任何事啊 是吧
Well, I guess I'm not in control of everything, am I?
真有意思 不是吗
funny, isn't it?
你可以用尽全力尝试 但是在眨眼之间
You can try and try, but in the blink of an eye...
你可能就会失去对你重要的一切
you can lose everything that matters to you.
爸 你还好吧
Dad, are you okay?
你们还不明白现在的情况吗
Don't you all see what's going on here?
老爸真的很想喝那杯牛奶
Dad really wanted that milk.
我今天差点就失去了你们所有人
I almost lost you guys today -- all of you.
就是那样
Just like that.
爹地
Aw, daddy.
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
你一整天都在试图掌控一切
You spent the whole day trying to control everything,
我这一整天却在试图不去掌控任何事
and I spent the entire day trying not to,
但两种方法都没奏效 不是吗
and neither way worked, did it?
是没有
Nope.
我或许会跟你唱反调
I may fight you on this,
但我需要你强迫我把乔琳2号也退回去
but I'm gonna need you to make me get rid of Jolene two.
-它很凶悍 -我知道
- She's a biter. - I know.
不过要等我们先拥抱完才行
As soon as we're done with this hug.
嘿 不管你们在干什么
Hey, whatever this is,
我都必须参与一下
I need to get in on it.
我今天差点死了
I almost died today.
-外公 -爸
- Grandpa. - Daddy.
爸啊
Aw, dad.
快过来
Come here.
都过来
Come here, you.
去驾校学学开车啊 婆娘
Learn how to drive, lady!
等我准备好了再去开会
I will get to the meeting when I get there.
我今天和死神擦肩而过
I looked death in the face today.
喂 好的 我想留个言
Hel-- hello. Yes, I would like to leave a message.
我丈夫之前预定了一台蛋壳色烘干机
My husband ordered an eggshell dryer --
不是爽身粉 不是羊皮纸
Not talc, not parchment
是蛋壳色的
-- eggshell.
你今天回来要早些啊 这是怎么了
You're home early. What happened to you?
那不重要
Doesn't matter.
我打电话给那个家电卖场了
So, I called that appliance store,
我要求他们务必
And I demanded that
把你想要的那台烘干机送到
you get the dryer that you wanted.
你的强硬态度一定奏效了
Oh, well, it must've worked
因为他们现在正把那台发错货的搬走呢
because they're taking away the wrong one right now.
愿意随时为你效劳 小公主
Anything for you, princess.
我都不认识你了 快过来 性感帅哥
Who's this guy? Get over here, sexy.
如果你想见识下什么叫性感 我...
If you want to see sexy, I just...
你身上是什么啊
What is all over you?
现在应该是你的鼻涕吧
Well, now you are.